Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1991-2010; 14
  - 2006, 15
    - Social Security, Reform/Privatization, 2006 (Box 399, Folder 9)
    - Tax, General, 2006 (Box 399, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Fair Tax, 2006 (Box 399, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Trade, General, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Trade, Trans Texas Corridor, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, General, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Airlines, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Veterans, General, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 6)
    - Veterans, Health Care/Disabilities (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 400, Folder 7)
    - Veterans, Health Care/Disabilities (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 400, Folder 8)
    - Welfare, 2006 (Box 400, Folder 9)
  - 2007, 16
    - General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - General, Thank Yous, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Animal Rights, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - Animal Rights, Animal Cruelty, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Banking, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 7)
    - Banking, Mortgages, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 8)
    - Budget, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 9)
    - Cities, A-Z, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights, Employment Non-Discrimination Act (ENDA), 2007 (Box 401, Folder 12)
    - Communications, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 13)
    - Communications, FCC, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 14)
    - Communications, Internet, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 15)
    - Communications, Telephone, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 16)
    - Communications, Television, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 17)
    - Criminal Justice, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 18)
    - Defense, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 19)
    - Defense, Don’t Ask Don’t Tell, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 20)
    - Defense, GI Bill, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 21)
    - Defense, Habeas Corpus, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 22)
    - Defense, Health Care, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 23)
    - Defense, Iraq War, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 24)
    - Defense, National Defense Authorization Act, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 25)
    - Defense, National Guard, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 26)
    - Defense, Torture, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 27)
    - Economy, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 28)
    - Education, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 29)
    - Education, Head Start, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 30)
    - Education, Higher Education, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 31)
    - Education, No Child Left Behind, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 32)
    - Education, Sex Education, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 33)
    - Education, Student Loans, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 34)
    - Education, TAKS Testing, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 35)
    - Education, Teacher’s Salary, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 36)
    - Energy, General, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 37)
    - Energy, Electricity, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 38)
    - Energy, Energy Bill, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 39)
    - Energy, Gas Prices, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 40)
    - Energy, Oil, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 41)
    - Energy, Renewable Energy, 2007 (Box 401, Folder 42)
    - Environment, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Environment, Air Quality, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Water Quality, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Affairs, Africa, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Affairs, Asia, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Affairs, Europe, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 9)
    - Government Affairs, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 10)
    - Government Affairs, Bush/Cheney Impeachment, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 11)
    - Gun Control, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 12)
    - Health, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 13)
    - Health, Cancer, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 14)
    - Health, Deficit Reduction Act, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 15)
    - Health, Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 2007 (Box 402, Folder 16)
    - Health, Hospitals, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 17)
    - Health, Insurance, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 18)
    - Health, Medicare, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 19)
    - Health, Mental Health, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 20)
    - Housing, General, 2007 (Box 402, Folder 21)
    - Immigration, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Immigration, Amnesty, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Immigration, Border Fence, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Immigration, English Language Act, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Immigration, H-2B Visas, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Immigration, SAVE Act, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Interior, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Judicial, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Labor, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - Religion, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - Social Security, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - Social Security, GPO/WEP, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - Tax, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 13)
    - Tax, Alternative Minimum Tax (AMT), 2007 (Box 403, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Cigarette Tax, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Fair Tax, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 16)
    - Tax. Internet Taxes, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 17)
    - Trade, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Aviation, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Highways, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Railways, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 22)
    - Transportation, Trans-Texas Corridor, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 23)
    - Transportation, Truck Driving, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 24)
    - Veterans, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, Benefits, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 26)
    - Veterans, Disabilities, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 27)
    - Veterans, Health Care, General, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 28)
    - Veterans, Hospitals and Clinics, 2007 (Box 403, Folder 29)
  - 2008, 17
    - General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - General, Thank Yous, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Abortion, Title X, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Farm Bill, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Animal Rights, General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Animal Rights, Animal Cruelty, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - Arts, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 9)
    - Banking, General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 10)
    - Banking, Credit Cards, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 11)
    - Banking, Mortgages, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 12)
    - Budget, General, 2008 (Box 404, Folder 13)
    - Budget, Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (1 of 4), 2008 (Box 404, Folder 14)
    - Budget, Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (2 of 4), 2008 (Box 404, Folder 15)
    - Budget, Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (3 of 4), 2008 (Box 404, Folder 16)
    - Budget, Emergency Economic Stabilization Act (4 of 4), 2008 (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Cities, A-Z, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, Marriage Protection Amendment, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Commerce, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 5)
    - Communications, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 6)
    - Communications, FCC, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 7)
    - Communications, Internet, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 8)
    - Communications, Telephone, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 9)
    - Communications, Television, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 11)
    - Defense, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 12)
    - Defense, Don’t Ask Don’t Tell, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Ft. Hood, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 14)
    - Defense, GI Bill, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 15)
    - Defense, Habeas Corpus, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 16)
    - Defense, Health Care, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 17)
    - Defense, Iraq War, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 18)
    - Defense, National Defense Authorization Act, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 19)
    - Defense, National Guard, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 20)
    - Defense, Torture, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 21)
    - Economy, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 22)
    - Education, General, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 23)
    - Education, Head Start, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 24)
    - Education, Higher Education, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 25)
    - Education, Mental Health, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 26)
    - Education, No Child Left Behind, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 27)
    - Education, Sex Education, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 28)
    - Education, Student Loans, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 29)
    - Education, TAKS Testing, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 30)
    - Education, Teacher’s Salary, 2008 (Box 405, Folder 31)
    - Employment, General, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Energy, General, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Energy, Electricity, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Energy Bill, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Energy, Gas Prices, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Energy, Nuclear Energy, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Energy, Oil (1 of 4), 2008 (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Energy, Oil (2 of 4), 2008 (Box 406, Folder 8)
    - Energy, Oil (3 of 4), 2008 (Box 406, Folder 9)
    - Energy, Oil (4 of 4), 2008 (Box 406, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Renewable Energy, 2008 (Box 406, Folder 11)
    - Environment, General, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Environment, Air Quality, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Bullhide Creek Sewer Plant, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Oil Drilling, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Water Quality, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Affairs, General, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Affairs, Africa, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Affairs, Asia, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Affairs, Europe, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 11)
    - Government Affairs, General (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 407, Folder 12)
    - Government Affairs, General (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 407, Folder 13)
    - Government Affairs, Presidential Endorsement, 2008 (Box 407, Folder 14)
    - Gun Control, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Health, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Health, Cancer, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Health, Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 2008 (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Health, Hospitals, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Health, Insurance, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Health, Medicare, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Health, Mental Health, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Housing, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 9)
    - Hunger Relief, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 10)
    - Immigration, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 11)
    - Immigration, Amnesty, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 12)
    - Immigration, Border Fence, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 13)
    - Immigration, English Language Act, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 14)
    - Immigration, H-2B Visas, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 15)
    - Immigration, SAVE Act, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 16)
    - Interior, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 17)
    - Judiciary, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 18)
    - Labor, General, 2008 (Box 408, Folder 19)
    - Religion, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Social Security, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Social Security, GPO/WEP, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Tax, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Tax, Alternative Minimum Tax (AMT), 2008 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - Tax, Bush Tax Cuts, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 6)
    - Tax, Cigarette Tax, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 7)
    - Tax, Fair Tax, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 8)
    - Tax, Federal Gas Tax, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Oil and Gas Taxes, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Tax Rebates for Illegal Immigrants, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 11)
    - Trade, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 12)
    - Trade, Columbia Free Trade Agreement, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 13)
    - Trade, Iran, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 14)
    - Trade, NAFTA, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 16)
    - Transportation, Aviation, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, Highways, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 18)
    - Transportation, National Speed Limit, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, Railways, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 20)
    - Transportation, Trans-Texas Corridor, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 21)
    - Transportation, Truck Driving, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 22)
    - Veterans, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 23)
    - Veterans, Agent Orange, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 24)
    - Veterans, Benefits, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 25)
    - Veterans, Disabilities, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 26)
    - Veterans, Health Care, General, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 27)
    - Veterans, Hospitals and Clinics, 2008 (Box 409, Folder 28)
- Vice Presidential Vetting, 2000-2008; 15
  This series contains copies of the documents Edwards provided Barack Obama’s Vice-Presidential Vetting Committee in 2008. The papers included the answers to 102 questions related to Edwards, his family, finances, business interests, election filings, legislative proposals, press conferences and releases, and voting record, with supporting documentation. This series also contains Edwards’s notes and memos, information on the vetting committee members, his stance on multiple issues, and strategies that could be used if he were selected. A small number of pages have redactions of social security numbers and the names of others to protect their privacy.
  - Chet Vice Presidential Notes and Memos, 2005-2008 (Box 410, Folder 1)
  - Obama vs. McCain Notebook (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 410, Folder 2)
  - Obama vs. McCain Notebook (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 410, Folder 3)
  - Vice Presidential Background Binder (1 of 4), 2000-2008 (Box 410, Folder 4)
  - Vice Presidential Background Binder (2 of 4), 2000-2008 (Box 410, Folder 5)
  - Vice Presidential Background Binder (3 of 4), 2000-2008 (Box 410, Folder 6)
  - Vice Presidential Background Binder (4 of 4), 2000-2008 (Box 410, Folder 7)